sscrecruitmentresults.in 2016-11-04

# Privacy Policy | Disclaimer

**Privacy Policy for sscrecruitmentresults.in**

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at keystroke59@gmail.com.

At sscrecruitmentresults.in, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by sscrecruitmentresults.in and how it is used.

**Log Files**  
Like many other Web sites, sscrecruitmentresults.in makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
sscrecruitmentresults.in does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

**DoubleClick DART Cookie**  
.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on sscrecruitmentresults.in.  
.:: Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to sscrecruitmentresults.in and other sites on the Internet.  
.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include ….  
Google Adsense

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on sscrecruitmentresults.in send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

sscrecruitmentresults.in has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. sscrecruitmentresults.in’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

If you require any more information or have any questions about our site’s disclaimer, please feel free to contact us by email at .

All the information on this website is published in good faith and for general information purpose only. http://sscrecruitmentresults.in/ does not make any warranties about the completeness, reliability and accuracy of this information. Any action you take upon the information you find on this website (http://sscrecruitmentresults.in/), is strictly at your own risk. http://sscrecruitmentresults.in/ will not be liable for any losses and/or damages in connection with the use of our website.

From our website, you can visit other websites by following hyperlinks to such external sites. While we strive to provide only quality links to useful and ethical websites, we have no control over the content and nature of these sites. These links to other websites do not imply a recommendation for all the content found on these sites. Site owners and content may change without notice and may occur before we have the opportunity to remove a link which may have gone ‘bad’.

Please be also aware that when you leave our website, other sites may have different privacy policies and terms which are beyond our control. Please be sure to check the Privacy Policies of these sites as well as their “Terms of Service” before engaging in any business or uploading any information.

### Consent

By using our website, you hereby consent to our disclaimer and agree to its terms.

### Update

This site disclaimer was last updated on: Sunday, October 5th, 2014  
_· Should we update, amend or make any changes to this document, those changes will be prominently posted here._
